Guide to the William Martin Religious Right research collection, 1975-2000 MS 537
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Subject files, 1978-1996 (Boxes 77-91)
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical subject files
    - Nixon (Box 81, Folder 14)
      Folder includes a summary from the archival tape log of "With God on Our Side," annotated news articles from 1981, and scans from Nixon's publically available presidential papers. Also some scans from the book entitled "The Nixon Theology."
    - Norquist, Grover (Box 81, Folder 15)
      Folder includes news articles scanned from the Washington Post, interview questions for Grover Norquist, and annotated news article transcripts from 1985-1993. Finally an article from Conservative Digest about Norquist entitled "Rising Young Stars."
    - Operation Rescue (Box 81, Folder 16)
      Folder includes newspaper articles from 1989 about the antiaportion movement's Operation Rescue and an abortion timeline from 1987-1994.
    - People for the American Way (Box 81, Folder 17)
      Folder includes scanned article from "The Advocate," a People for the American Way map of focus states, newspaper, memos, and People for the American Way pamphlets, newsletters. Also included communication between People for the American Way and Luminere Productions, a long list of authors and titles, and an annotated list from People for the American Way notes on shows. Also includes a anti-Christian Coalition newsletter, and a anti-Focus on the Family newsletter, along with two articles from People for the American Way about Pat Robertson as an extremist.
    - Phillips, Howard (Box 81, Folder 18)
      Folder includes information about Phillips the President of the Conservative Caucus and the founder of the United States Taxpayers Party (USTP). Also has an interview transcript, newsletters from Chalcedon, and scanned newspaper articles from the mid 1980s. Also has articles by Phillips, from the 1983 Review of the News, and the 1982 Conservative Manifesto. Also, a memo about Phillips and his beliefs about Falwell,and the relationship between the Conservative Caucus and Moral Majority. A transcript from 1987 Meet the Press featuring Phillips about the AIDS crisis, a policy review of major religious right thinkers on who to replace Reagan, and an article about Phillips attempt to start the USTP.
    - Photos (Box 81, Folder 19)
      Folder includes scans of a number of photos, mostly unlabeled, from news articles along with scans of news articles on figures such as Robertson which contain images, and photos in news articles contain captions.
    - Pippert, Becky (Box 81, Folder 20)
      Folder includes a scan of an article from Today's Christian Woman which features an interview of Pippert, a self professed "professional evangelist."
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 81, Folder 21)
      Articles includes newsletters from Front Lines Research, a pro-Planned Parenthood organization, from 1994 and 1995 about their response to antiabortion advocates. Also includes an article produced by the Missouri Citizen Education Fund and the Missouri Progressive Vote Coalition from 1995, "The Missouri 1st Militia, Republican Politicians and The Violent Right: Tracing the Connections." Finally a book entitled "Without Justice for All: A report on the Christian Right in Sacramento and Beyond," by the Planned Parenthood of Sacramento Valley.
    - Political Research Association (Box 81, Folder 22)
      Folder includes an anti-right wing policy think tank, a copy of their March 1994 journal "The Public Eye on Religious Right Extremism," and a memo on "Conceptualizing the U.S. Political Right." Finally another edition of their journal on Constructing Homophobia.
    - Pro-Family Movement (Box 81, Folder 23)
      Folder includes a list from the Conservative Digest of the leaders of the Pro-family movement in Washington and in the general public, with highlights and annotations, and an interesting diagram on how these groups interact with each other.
    - Promise Keepers (1 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 24)
      Folder includes a pamphlet from the Christian Service Brigade, an associated organization to Promise Keepers, the original May 1995 edition of Charisma and Christian Life about Promise Keepers. A pamphlet from the International Congress on the Family from 1995,a publication from Promise Keepers, and a newsletter from Men of Action. Finally the folder included a Promise Keepers folder about their 1995 conference.
    - Promise Keepers (2 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 25)
      - Promise Keepers Misc. (Box 81, Folder 25, Subfolder 1)
        Folder included Promise Keepers 1995 Media highlights tape transcript, scanned news articles, transcripts of other news articles, and scanned journal article from "Church and State: from Promise Keepers." Also an annotated sermon of Dr. E. V. Hill, an annotated interview transcript of Mel White, and an article from Sports Illustrated, original magazine articles, and other scanned news articles.
      - Research Leads (Box 81, Folder 25, Subfolder 2)
        Folder includes handwritten notes about news articles, and men and two religious life archival search (86 records).
      - E. V. Hill (Box 81, Folder 25, Subfolder 3)
        Folder includes a transcript of news articles and T.V. shows, annotated, E. V. Hill "Maintaining the Momentum from Promise Keepers" publications (poor quality). A magazine article titled "America's 15 Greatest Black Preachers," along with E. V. Hill resume/list of positions.
      - Tony Evans (Box 81, Folder 25, Subfolder 4)
        Folder inclduded 1995 editions of "The Alternative View an Urban Christian Alternative, and City light," and three other publicatons.
    - Promise Keepers (3 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 26)
      - Promise Keepers - General (Box 81, Folder 26, Subfolder 1)
        Folder includes a research printout with a highlighted list of the role of Promise Keepers, a booklet entitled "The Brigade Trail" from the Christian Service Brigade, and other publications from Brigade Leader. The folder includes scans of newspaper from the mid-1990s about Promise Keepers, a article "God and the Gridiron," handwritten notes, and a piece of original newspaper from the New York Times. Finally discussion of productions with Lumiere and a article entitled "A Triumph of his Will."
      - Promise Keepers Publications/Info (Box 81, Folder 26, Subfolder 2)
        Folder includes 1996 clergy conference from Promise Keepers booklet, promise keepers memos, and newsletters. Alongside there are is a Men of Action 1994 booklet, and booklet from Keepers Promise Men's COnferences 1996.
    - Dan Quayle (Box 81, Folder 27)
      Folder includes news articles from Nation that area scanned about Dan Quayle, H. W. Bush's V. P., a book review of Pat Robertson's "The New World Order."
    - Reagan Administration (1 of 3), 1980-1984 (Box 81, Folder 28)
      - Reagan Administration, 1980-1984 (Box 81, Folder 28, Subfolder 1)
        Folder includes scanned news articles from New York Times and the Washington Times and the political nature of Moral Majority. There is also a report card of the Family Policy Advisory Board on the first term of Reagan. There is also information organizing Conservative Political Action Committee's and a newsletter from the Leadership Action. There was also a number of newspaper scans from 1982 and a magazine article from The Christian Century "Reagan and the Evangelicals: The Making of A Love Affair." There was also a transcript of Reagan's remarks to the National Association of Evangelicals in 1983, remarks of George H. W. Bush at Liberty College in 1983, and article from the 1991 Church and State "California Dreamin." Finally there is information about National Endowment of the Arts and National Endowment for the Humanities and censorship, some original newspaper, and a report for People for the American Way.
      - Reagan, Ronald (Box 81, Folder 28, Subfolder 2)
        Folder includes scanned news articles from 1984, and an article from The Atlantic Monthly, "Ronald Reagan and the Techniques of Deception" 1984. Finally there was Reagan's speech to the National Religious Broadcasters and a book review of reports on Reagan.
      - Reagan - Gov. Campaign, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 28, Subfolder 3)
        Folder includes a scanned chapter of "Reagan and Reality" from 1970 with annotations and highlights.
    - Reagan Administration (2 of 3), 1980-1984 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Family Protection Act (Box 82, Folder 1, Subfolder 1)
      - School Prayer & Reagan (Box 82, Folder 1, Subfolder 2)
    - Reagan Administration (3 of 3), 1980-1984 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Evangelical Vote & Ronald Reagan (Box 82, Folder 2, Subfolder 1)
      - Campaign, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 2, Subfolder 2)
      - Campaign, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 2, Subfolder 3)
      - Reagan Speech Excerpts (Box 82, Folder 2, Subfolder 4)
      - Howell Rains on Reagan 1st Term (Box 82, Folder 2, Subfolder 5)
    - Reconstructionism (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Reconstruction (Box 82, Folder 3, Subfolder 1)
      - Schaeffer (Box 82, Folder 3, Subfolder 2)
    - Regent University (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Reed, Ralph (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Religion (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Religion: Propaganda (Box 82, Folder 6, Subfolder 1)
      - Religion: International (Box 82, Folder 6, Subfolder 2)
      - Religion: General (Box 82, Folder 6, Subfolder 3)
      - Pledge of Allegiance (Box 82, Folder 6, Subfolder 4)
    - Research (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Research Articles - Religious Right (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Religious Right: General (Box 82, Folder 8, Subfolder 1)
      - Wall Street Journal: Values Crisis (Box 82, Folder 8, Subfolder 2)
      - Gay & Lesbian Issues - Religious Right (Box 82, Folder 8, Subfolder 3)
      - Women & the Religious Right (Box 82, Folder 8, Subfolder 4)
    - Research Articles (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Religious Right: Post '92 Notes (Box 82, Folder 9, Subfolder 1)
      - Religious Right: Bob Maddox (Box 82, Folder 9, Subfolder 2)
      - Religious Right: Iran/Contra (Box 82, Folder 9, Subfolder 3)
    - Religious Right: General (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Religious Right (1 of 2) (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Reagan & R. R. (Box 82, Folder 11, Subfolder 1)
      - Religious Right: Pre-1960s & 1960s (Box 82, Folder 11, Subfolder 2)
      - Religious Right: Marketing/Corporatism (Box 82, Folder 11, Subfolder 3)
      - Religious Right: Jewish Ties (Box 82, Folder 11, Subfolder 4)
      - Religious Right & 1996 Campaign (Box 82, Folder 11, Subfolder 5)
      - Religious Right & The GOP (Box 82, Folder 11, Subfolder 6)
      - Religious Right: Economic Issues (Box 82, Folder 11, Subfolder 7)
    - Religious Right (2 of 2) (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - Religious Right: Religious Criticism (Box 82, Folder 12, Subfolder 1)
      - Religious Right: Political Organizing (Box 82, Folder 12, Subfolder 2)
      - Religious Right & Republicans (Box 82, Folder 12, Subfolder 3)
      - Religious Right Funding (Box 82, Folder 12, Subfolder 4)
      - Racial Reconciliation (Box 82, Folder 12, Subfolder 5)
      - Founders/Money Trail (Box 82, Folder 12, Subfolder 6)
      - Religious Right - Critical Analysis (Box 82, Folder 12, Subfolder 7)
    - Religious Right: Core Articles (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Religious Roundtable (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Resist (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Religious and Theological Studies Fellowship (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Resources (1 of 2) (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Resources (2 of 2) (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - The Right (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - Religious Right: Criticism (Box 82, Folder 19, Subfolder 1)
      - The Right: General (Box 82, Folder 19, Subfolder 2)
    - Right Wing Literature (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Robertson, Pat (1 of 5) (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - Pat Robertson (Box 82, Folder 21, Subfolder 1)
      - State Politics, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 21, Subfolder 2)
      - Pat Robertson (Post 1988) (Box 82, Folder 21, Subfolder 3)
    - Robertson, Pat (2 of 5) (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - CBN & Latin America (Box 82, Folder 22, Subfolder 1)
      - Pat Robertson, General (Box 82, Folder 22, Subfolder 2)
    - Robertson, Pat (3 of 5) (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Robertson, Pat (4 of 5) (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Pat Robertson (5 of 5) (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Robertson & Michigan (Box 83, Folder 3, Subfolder 1)
      - Robertson & Iowa (Box 83, Folder 3, Subfolder 2)
      - Nuttle, Marc (Box 83, Folder 3, Subfolder 3)
      - Constance Snapp - Robertson Campaign (Box 83, Folder 3, Subfolder 4)
      - Robertson Footage (Box 83, Folder 3, Subfolder 5)
      - Robertson - Timeline (Box 83, Folder 3, Subfolder 6)
    - Robison, James (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Schaeffer, Francis (1 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Schaeffer, Francis (2 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Schafly, Phyllis (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - School Prayer, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - School Prayer, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - School Prayer, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 9, Subfolder 1)
      - School Prayer Amendment (Box 83, Folder 9, Subfolder 2)
    - School Prayer, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Scopes Trial (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Secular Humanism (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Sekulow, Jay (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Seminar Notes (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Sex Education (1 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Sex Education (2 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Sex Ed - General (Box 83, Folder 16, Subfolder 1)
      - Signed Releases (Box 83, Folder 16, Subfolder 2)
      - YFC Talent Services (Box 83, Folder 16, Subfolder 3)
      - Sex Ed - Anahiem (Box 83, Folder 16, Subfolder 4)
    - Sheldon, Lou (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Sider, Ron (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Southern Baptist Convention (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Statistics - Election, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Swaggart, Jimmy (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Summit Ministries (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Tabernacle Baptist Church (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Tax Information: 501 Status (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Telescandals (Box 83, Folder 26)
      - Telescandals Research/Books (Box 83, Folder 26, Subfolder 1)
      - Telescandals - Timeline (Box 83, Folder 26, Subfolder 2)
      - Telescandal Articles (Box 83, Folder 26, Subfolder 3)
      - Telescandal Article Research (Box 83, Folder 26, Subfolder 4)
    - Terry, Randall (1 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Terry, Randall (2 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Clarence Thomas (Box 84, Folder 2, Subfolder 1)
      - Reconstructionism - Randall Terry (Box 84, Folder 2, Subfolder 2)
    - Tikkun (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Town Hall (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Viguerie, Richard (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Wead, Doug (1 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Wead, Doug (2 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Wead, Doug (3 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Weinhold, Dick (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - White House Working Group on the Family (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Weyrich, Paul (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Paul Weyrich (Box 84, Folder 11, Subfolder 1)
      - Net (TV) (Box 84, Folder 11, Subfolder 2)
    - White, Mel (1 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - White, Mel (2 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - White House Conference on the Family (1 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - JoAnn Gasper (Box 84, Folder 14, Subfolder 1)
      - Jim Patton - Christian Harvest Times (Box 84, Folder 14, Subfolder 2)
      - Memos - J. C. (Box 84, Folder 14, Subfolder 3)
      - Iowa WHCF (Box 84, Folder 14, Subfolder 4)
      - "Pro-Family" (Box 84, Folder 14, Subfolder 5)
      - Footage - WHCF (Box 84, Folder 14, Subfolder 6)
      - Docs Ref - WHCF (Box 84, Folder 14, Subfolder 7)
    - White House Conference on Families (2 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Whittlesey, Faith (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Youth For Christ (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Zeoli, Billy (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Unlabeled (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Subseries B: Other subject files
    - Christian New Right (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Christian New Right: Election, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Christian New Right: Elections, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Christian New Right: Elections, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Christian New Right: Elections, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Christian New Right: Elections, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Christian New Right: Elections, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Christian New Right: Elections, 1996 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Christian New Right: Legal Groups (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Christian New Right: Criticism (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Christian New Right: Parental Rights (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Christian New Right: Politics (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Christian New Right: Polls (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Christian New Right: Promise Keepers (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Christian New Right: Race (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Christian New Right: Reconstructionists (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Christian New Right: Republicans (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Christian New Right: Politics - Reconstructionalist (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Christian New Right: Schaeffer (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Christian New Right: Schafly Eagle Forum (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Christian New Right: Summit Ministries (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Christian New Right: Welfare (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Christian New Right: Women (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Christian New Right: Articles on Religious Right (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Christian New Right: General (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Christian Right: Articles about (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Religious & Society - Politics - Religious Right (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Christian Right: Books about/notes (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Christian Right: Church and state/constitution (1 of 4) (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Christian Right: Church and State/Constitution (2 of 4) (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Christian Right: Church and State/Constitution (3 of 4) (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Christian Right: Church and State/Constitution (4 of 4) (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archives Materials (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archives Materials - Handwritten Notes (1 of 6) (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials Processing Notes (1 of 3) (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials - Handwritten Notes (2 of 6) (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials - Charles W. Colson (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials - William B. Martin Presidential Notes (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials Processing Notes (2 of 3) (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Christian Right Nixon Archival Materials - Processing Notes (3 of 3) (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Christian Right; Nixon Archival Materials - Handwritten Notes (3 of 6) (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials - Handwritten Notes (4 of 6) (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials - Handwritten Notes (5 of 6) (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials - Handwritten Notes (6 of 6) (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials - Copies (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials - Billy Graham (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Christian Right: Nixon Archival Materials - Contact List (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - Religious Right: Abortion (1 of 3) (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Religious Right: Abortion (2 of 3) (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Religious Right: Abortion (3 of 3) (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Religious Right: AIDS (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Religious Right: Creationism (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Religious Right: Evolution vs. Creationism (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Religion and Society: Science (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Religion and Society: Evolution; Creation (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Religion and Society: Science - Creation (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Religious Right: Culture, Culture wars (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Religious Right: Economics (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Religious Right: Family (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Religious Right: Health Care (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Religion and Society: Family (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Religious Right: Homosexuality (1 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Religious Right: Homosexuality (2 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Religious Right: Media (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Religious Right: Militias/Military (1 of 2) (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: General (1 of 3) (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: General (2 of 3) (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: General (3 of 3) (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: Americans United (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: American United (2 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: Citizens Project - Colorado (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: Institution for First Amendment Studies (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: People for the American Way (1 of 4) (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: People for American Way (2 of 4) (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: People for American Way (3 of 4) (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: People for American Way (4 of 4) (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: Political Research Association (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: Texas Freedom Network (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: Texas Faith Network (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: George Pravdenko (1 of 3) (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: George Pravdenko (2 of 3) (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Opposition to Religious Right: George Pravdenko (3 of 3) (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Campus Crusade (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Christianity Today (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Pat Robertson Questions (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Telescandals (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - C. Everett Koop, Rev. Jimmy Allen - AIDS (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Reagan Articles (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Library of Virginia - Image Copies (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Archival Stills (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Research Articles: Episode 6, Dobson, Reed etc. (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Episode 6 Photos (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Doug Wead (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Ethics and Public Policy Center (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Bennett - Anthology (Show 6) (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Misc. Evangelical Documents (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Scanned Newspaper Articles (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Carter Transcripts (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Carter and Christianity (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Jimmy Carter Public Papers about Religion (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Carl Henry Notes (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Robertson - Bed-Stuy (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Robison v. WFAA (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Additional Articles (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Newsweek/Times Magazine, 1976-1980 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Misc. Research Articles (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - School Prayer (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Evangelical Doubts About Political Involvement (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Systematic Theology Project (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Articles and Letters from LAD (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - Misc. Article and photo (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - Religious Right Sources; Transparencies for Lecture (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Seminar Notes, 1995-05-28-1995-05-29 (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - Joe Dumit - New Age Cults (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - New Age Cults: The Way International (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - New Age Cults, Misc. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Religious Right Articles (1 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Religious Right Articles (2 of 2) (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - JFK (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Items used for Proposal (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Reagan Documents (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - School Prayer Documents (Box 90, Folder 9)